再给你讲个有趣的气象小知识
And here's another interesting weather fact.
又一个? 太好了!
Another? Great!
喷流的变化可以影响到
Changes in jet streams can affect the speed
地球的自转速度
at which the Earth rotates on its axis,
所以坏天气真的可以使一天变长
so bad weather can actually make the day longer.
这么说 现在世界上肯定有个地方在刮风暴
Well, there must be a hell of a storm somewhere.
随便开玩笑吧
Joke if you must,
但你会怀念这些时刻的
but you're going to miss these moments.
再几天Leonard就回来了
With Leonard home in a few days,
这是你最后一次载我去购物了
this was your last time driving me to the grocery store.
嗯 我会想念的
You know, I will miss this.
跟你说 要是我的苹果是面的
I'll tell you what, if my apples are mealy,
我们就再去农品部来个大采购
we'll hit the produce section for one last crazy blowout.
这次你可以推购物车
Heck, you can even push the cart.
请不要把我对Leonard回家的盼望看成是
Please don't take my looking forward to Leonard's return
对这些天你所做工作的批评
as criticism of the job you've been doing in his absence.
我不会的
I won't.
批评会晚点写在你的报告卡上
That criticism will come later in your report card.
不过没人能管我
Yeah, I didn't stay for the detention,
我不会看报告卡的
I'm not gonna read the report card.
你好
Hello.
Leonard啊!
Leonard!
嘘 嘘! 嗨!
Shh, shh. Hi!
小声点 哦 天呐
Keep your voice down. Oh, my God.
你不是星期天才回来吗?
You weren't supposed to be here till Sunday!
我们实验提前做完了
We finished the experiment early,
所以我想回来给你个惊喜
so I thought I'd come home and surprise you.
哦 我的天 为什么我们要小声说话?
Oh, my gosh, why are we whispering?
我还没告诉Sheldon
I didn't tell Sheldon,
这样我们就可以单独过几天了
so we could have a few days alone.
哦 这太浪漫了
Oh, that is so romantic.
呃 是啊 我就是这么想的
Uh, sure, that's why I did it.
哦... 我还是不敢相信你回来了
Oh... I just cannot believe you're here.
Penny 你今天走运了!
Penny, it's your lucky day!
有三个鸡蛋显然不是巨大号的
Three of the eggs are clearly not jumbo.
拿钥匙走吧
Grab your keys.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季第二集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：影子
时间轴：潇妹纸
翻译：Hunter鱼 波特妹子 进击的千欲
校对：UU在美帝苦逼
呃 Stuart 我在想
Uh, Stuart, I was wondering
你是否能帮我找样东西
if you could help me find something.
很乐意 除非是找希望或者活下去的原因
Happy to, unless it's hope or a reason to live.
哦 你把我逗乐了 悲催的孩子
Oh, you make me laugh, sad clown.
不管怎样...
Anyhoo...
Leonard几天后就会回来
Leonard will be back in a couple days
我得给他准备个欢迎礼物
and I need a welcome-home gift for him.
由于他去的是海上 也许
As he's been at sea, perhaps something
航海主题的东西比较合适吧
with a nautical theme might be appropriate.
嗯 好吧 我不知道你的预算是多少
Okay, well, I don't know how much you want to spend,
但我这儿确实有个很酷的水行侠雕像
but I do have this pretty cool Aquaman statue.
水行侠?
Aquaman?
哦 这可不是个搞笑礼物 Stuart
Oh, this isn't a gag gift, Stuart.
差不多吧
Yeah, just as well.
这是个很稀有的
It's a pretty rare piece.
我倒更愿意卖给一个真正的收藏家
I'd rather just sell it to a real collector.
我是个真正的收藏家啊
I'm a real collector.
有多稀有?
How rare is it?
我就不该提到它的
Oh, I shouldn't even have mentioned it.
来个蝙蝠侠喷水枪怎么样?
How about a Batman squirt gun?
别想勾引我去买一个
Don't try and trick me
我不想买的东西
into buying something I don't want.
接着说水行侠
Now let's talk Aquaman.
他们在想什么啊 把章鱼博士的大脑放进
What were they thinking, putting Doctor Octopus's mind
蜘蛛侠的身体?
in Spider-Man's body?
好吧 我其实很喜欢看
Well, I've been quite enjoying that.
它结合了蜘蛛侠超级英雄的乐趣
It combines all the superhero fun of Spider-Man
和"辣妈辣妹"的换位把戏
with all the body-switching shenanigans of Freaky Friday.
两个版本: 原版和洛翰版的
Both versions: original and Lohan.
"两个版本: 原版和洛翰版的"
"Both versions: original and Lohan."
你就是个白痴
You're an idiot.
嘿 你怎么了?
Hey, what's your problem?
抱歉 我最近有些暴躁
I'm sorry, I've been kind of snippy lately.
估计是节食的原因
It's probably this stupid diet I'm on.
你为啥要节食啊?
Why are you on a diet?
我长了好几磅
I've put on a couple pounds.
不得不到男装部买裤子了
Had to buy these pants in the men's section.
好吧 我们都见过你老妈了
Well, we've all seen your mom.
龙生龙凤生凤
That Butterball turkey
基因是不骗人的
was bound to come home to roost.
1200美元! 不能再多了!
$1,200! That's my final offer!
好吧 Sheldon 你赢了
All right, Sheldon, you win.
我敢肯定Leonard会喜欢得不得了
I'm sure Leonard is gonna love this.
哦 对了 Leonard的礼物
Oh, right, a present for Leonard.
你最好把那把水枪也放进来吧
You better throw in that squirt gun.
对了 我也不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
这把水枪 它 呃 它也很稀有
This squirt gun, it's, uh, it's pretty rare.
喔
Ooh.
这是我在船上摆的泰坦尼克姿势
And this is me doing the Titanic pose on the boat.
啊
Ah.
还有... 哦
And... oh.
那是我掉水里了在被救
That's me getting rescued after I fell in.
哦
Oh.
哦 是匹萨到了
Oh, that's the pizza.
是的
Yep.
- 给你些钱  - 谢谢
- Here's some money.  - Thank you.
我要去撞个头了
And I'm gonna hit the head.
这是我们这帮老水手们
That's what us salty sea dogs say
要去尿尿的说法
when we have to go pee-pee.
- 嘿  - 22.5美元
- Hey.  - $22.50.
好的 这是 呃 25块钱 都给你了
Okay, here's, uh, $25. Keep the change.
真的?
Seriously?
我刚刚爬了有四层楼梯啊
I just walked up, like, four flights of stairs.
哦
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 这是 呃...
Well, here's, um...
三十多美分
30-something cents
而且我保证我不会告诉你老板
and a promise I won't call your boss
你一身大麻味儿
and tell him you reek of marijuana.
哦 Penny 你叫了匹萨
Oh, Penny, I see you've ordered pizza.
我买了中国食物
I have Chinese food.
真好
That's nice.
哦 好天然的古龙水啊
Oh, that's a rather earthy cologne.
我叔叔之前常常用
My uncle used to wear that.
也许在Leonard回来之前我们可以
Perhaps we can enjoy one last meal together
- 最后共享一次晚餐  - 是啊 谢谢
- before Leonard returns.  - Yeah, thanks,
但我今晚有点想自己一个人吃 所以...
but I kind of feel like eating alone tonight, so...
你确定?
Are you sure?
有了你的意大利匹萨和我的中国面条
With your Italian pizza and my Chinese noodles,
我们可以玩马可・波罗
we could play Marco Polo.
当然 我是说 重现一下威尼斯探险家
I mean, of course, a reenactment of a meal
马克・波罗生前的餐饭
in the life of Marco Polo the Venetian explorer,
而不是那个叫马可・波罗的恐怖水上游戏
not Marco Polo the terrifying water sport.
是啊 听起来很有意思 但谢谢不了
Uh, yeah, it sounds fun, but no thanks.
晚安哈!
Have a good night!
什么... 你有伴儿了?
What, now... do you have company?
不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
知道吗? 马桶最近老这样
You know what? Th-The toilet's been doing that.
我叫了楼管 所以...
I called the building manager, so...
- 哦 我可以帮你看看  - 呃...
- Oh, I can take a look at it.  - Well...
我修水管很熟练
I'm quite familiar with plumbing.
不是吹的
Not to brag,
五年级一年我的头几乎都埋在马桶里面过的
but I spent most of fifth grade with my head in a toilet.
是啊 不 不 不
Yeah, no, no, no.
知道吗 Sheldon 没事的
You know what, Sheldon, it's okay.
你没必要到洗手间去
You don't have to go into the bathroom.
真让人好奇
That's curious.
要是这里没别人
If there's no one here,
桌上为什么摆了两杯红酒?
why are there two glasses of wine on the table?
哦
Oh.
呃 你知道 我有两只手
Well, you know, I-I've got two hands
还有点嗜酒
and a bit of a drinking problem.
当然
Of course.
问了个傻问题
Ask a silly question.
哦
Oh.
真奇怪
That's odd.
呃 什么?
Um, what?
垃圾桶里面有
There are takeout containers
外卖的盒子
in the trash can.
那又怎样? 那是我昨晚上吃的
So? That's my dinner from last night.
奇怪的是它们在垃圾桶里面
What's odd is they're in the trash can.
好吧
Okay.
听着 宝贝儿 我向你保证这里没人
Look, honey, I promise there's no one's here.
我干了一天活
I've had a long day.
就是想安安静静一个人吃个晚饭
I just want to have a quiet dinner by myself.
哦 好吧
Oh, very well.
我也常常会享受独处的乐趣
I'm no stranger to enjoying the pleasures of solitude.
- 哦!  - 什么?
- Oh!  - What?
你有给Leonard买欢迎礼物了吗?
Have you gotten Leonard a welcome-home gift yet?
- 没  - 哦 太好了
- No.  - Oh, great.
你想不想跟我一起送一个
Do you want to go halfsies
两百块的喷水枪?
on a $200 squirt gun?
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, honey.
嘿
Hey.
我做了巧克力蛋糕 要不要来一个?
I made some brownies. You want one?
你在开玩笑吗 啊?
You're kidding, right?
你知道
I mean, you know
我正减肥呢
I'm trying to lose weight.
天 我以为在婚姻中夫妻应同心协力
God, I thought we were partners in this marriage.
是同心的 别埋怨了
We are. Stop it.
而且最后再说一次 你不胖
And for the last time, you're not fat.
是吗? 跟体重秤说去
Really? Tell that to the bathroom scale,
因为你们其中一个在撒谎
'cause one of you is lying.
好吧 当我没问
Fine, forget I asked.
在你妈家吃的晚饭怎么样?
How was dinner at your mom's?
很糟糕
Awful.
我又得帮她全身擦药膏
I had to rub her ointment all over her again.
她干嘛不自己来?
Why can't she do it?
因为我们母子关系亲密得不正常
'Cause we've got a deeply unhealthy relationship.
这倒提醒我了
Which reminds me,
你能从实验室弄点这个样品吗?
do you think you can get any samples of this from work?
本来够她用一个月的
This was supposed to last her a month,
但医生没考虑到
but they didn't take into account
她后背的面积
the square footage of her back.
我看看
Let me see.
你帮她擦药膏多久了?
How long have you been putting this on her?
不记得了
I don't know.
几个星期吧 怎么了?
Few weeks. Why?
这是非常强的雌激素药膏
This is really strong estrogen cream.
别告诉我你没戴手套
Please tell me you've been wearing gloves.
这肿成香肠的手能戴上手套嘛
Like these swollen sausages could fit in gloves.
Howei 雌激素被你的皮肤吸收了
Howie, the estrogen's getting absorbed by your skin.
所以你才
That's why you've been
浮肿 易怒 特别欠抽
all bloated and moody and a giant pain in the ass.
你全身都是雌激素也没这样啊
You're full of estrogen and you don't act like that.
因为我是女的
That's 'cause I'm a woman.
专业驾驭这猛兽几十年了
I've had years of practice riding the dragon.
好吧
Fine.
下次我会戴手套的
I'll wear gloves next time.
但荷尔蒙完全从你体内排出
It's still gonna take a few weeks
还需要好几个星期
for the hormones to leave your system.
我真是又傻
I feel so stupid.
又胖
And fat.
没关系的
It's okay.
在我心中你仍然最美
You still look great to me.
这样吧 要不我们去卧室里
In fact, why don't we go in the bedroom
我证明给你看啊?
and I'll prove it to you?
做爱? 不是吧?
Sex? Really?
你就会来这一套!
I mean, that's just your solution to everything!
哦 还有个有趣的事
Oh, and here's a fun thing.
我想到了两个不同的单词
I worked it out so that there are
描述勺子
two different words for spoon:
(Planko Montoya一种运动 用短木棍击球防止落地；Janko一种怪物，需要处女献祭，也指很长的鲸鱼阴茎)
"planko"和"janko."
"planko" and "janko."
"Planko"指有食物的勺子
"Planko" is a spoon with food,
"janko"指没食物的勺子
"janko" is a spoon without food.
(ptang代指阴道，所以是"空"的)
"Janko"结尾还有不发音的"ptang"
"Janko" is spelled with a silent "ptang."
Sheldon 你根本就没在听
Sheldon, you're not even listening
我新编语言的规则
to the rules of my made-up language.
我听着呢
Yes, I am.
那"tweepadock"什么意思?
Then what does "tweepadock" mean?
呃...
Uh...
大象?
elephant?
(大家先猜一下为什么 解释在片源最后)
算你走运
Lucky guess.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只是被之前Penny那发生的事
I'm just distracted by something
分心了
that happened over at Penny's.
怎么了?
What happened?
我觉得Penny对Lenard不忠了
I fear Penny is being unfaithful to Leonard.
什么?
What?
她说自己是一个人
She claimed to be alone
但明显还有别人在她房间
when there was obviously someone else in her apartment.
我别无选择只能做最坏的打算
I have no choice but to assume the worst,
因为Leonard出海考察
given Leonard's lengthy sea voyage
她的地狱之门又极其贪婪
and her famously ravenous nether regions.
我觉得Penny不会背叛Leonard的
I don't think Penny would cheat on Leonard.
你确定?
Oh, really?
我们曾经有一次对视比赛
She and I once had a staring contest.
她大声拍手让我眨眼了
She clapped really loud and made me blink.
作弊和劈腿只有一线之差
It's a small leap from there to sexual infidelity.
你别胡说了
You're being ridiculous.
Amy 她的中国菜饭盒
Amy, there were Chinese food containers...
是在垃圾桶"里"的
in the trash can.
可怜的Leonard
Poor Leonard.
听到什么了吗?
Do you hear anything?
有一个女人的声音
I hear a woman's voice.
是Penny吗?
Is it Penny?
不 是你
No, it's you.
好吧 我听到低声私语和笑声了
All right, I hear whispering and giggling.
现在有接吻的声音
Now I think I hear kissing.
切 你知道接吻什么声音吗
Yeah, like you know what kissing sounds like.
星际迷航里见过 小样
There's kissing in Star Trek, smarty-pants.
让我听听
Let me listen.
好像是Leonard的声音
Sounds like Leonard.
拜托
Please.
Leonard干嘛提前回家
Why would Leonard come home early
浪费时间吻Penny
and waste his time kissing Penny
他完全可以和他最好的小伙伴玩耍啊?
when he could be hanging out with his best buddy?
不管了
Yeah, that's it.
我要捉奸在床了
I'm catching her in the act.
别 Sheldon 别
No, Sheldon, don't.
抓到了!
Aha!
搞什么?!
What the hell?!
真是你 Leonard?
Leonard?
Sheldon 你不能就那么闯进来的!
Sheldon, you cannot just barge in here like that!
没错
Right.
Penny开门!
Penny!
Penny开门! Penny开门!
Penny! Penny!
你要开门吗?
Are you going to answer the door?
还是我再开门 再抓你们一次?
Should I open and say "Aha!" again?
对不起 Sheldon
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
我应该告诉你我回来了
I should've told you I was back.
我只是想和Penny过几天二人世界
I just wanted to have a couple days alone with Penny.
不不 该道歉的是我
Oh, no, I should apologize.
我没有意识到我们的友谊
Uh, I never realized to what extent
让你如此难以承受
our friendship was a burden to you.
这么说不对
That is not fair.
我一个月至少抱怨一次受不了了
I complain about what a burden it is at least once a month.
别别别 请不要美化这件事
Oh, no, no, let's not sugarcoat this.
你就是觉得我挑剔 卖弄 而且烦人
You find me finicky, pedantic and annoying.
他没有
No, he doesn't.
我之前确实一字不差地说过
I actually have used those exact words before.
也是这个顺序
In that order.
好吧 Leonard 我觉得是时候
Well, Leonard, I think it's high time
说出"大象"了("大"声说出真"相")
you and I address the "tweepadock" in the room.
啥?
The what?
- 解释一下 Amy?  - 别把我扯进来
- Amy?  - Please leave me out of this.
呃... 好吧
Uh... fine.
Leonard啊
Leonard,
你没必要再继续
there's no need for you
假装喜欢我了
to pretend to like me anymore.
别这样 我都道歉过了
Come on, I said I was sorry.
不不 你的道歉还是留到
No, no, you save your apologies
和Penny做爱不欢的时候说吧
for after you've had disappointing coitus with Penny.
其实还好啦
It was fine.
拜托 别傻了
Come on, this is silly.
对了 我这次出门
Hey, um, I brought you back
给你带回一个小礼物 不错吧?
a little present from my trip, huh?
是你想要的水手帽
It's that sailor cap that you wanted.
挺赞的 是吧?
It's neat, huh?
你真的以为一个破纪念品
You honestly think you can buy back my friendship
就能买回我的友谊吗?
with a cheap souvenir?
不是的
I don't.
真的不是
No, I really don't.
试试嘛
Just try it on.
好看啊
Oh, yeah.
- 你好 水手  - 哦 这才是正点
- Hello, sailor.  - Ooh, now we're talking.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
这改变不了什么
This changes nothing.
不过今年万圣节的服装
Except the Halloween costume
会变一下
I'm wearing this year.
Amy 你要扮成奥丽弗(大力水手中女主角)
Amy, you're going to be Olive Oyl.
别吃太胖
Lay off the donuts.
感谢你过来
Thanks for coming over.
没什么
No problem.
哦 你做了小三明治!
Ooh, you made little sandwiches!
是啊 这是黄瓜和奶油芝士
Yeah, that's cucumber and cream cheese.
还有鸡肉和罗甘莓
That's turkey and loganberry.
别告诉我的屁股 但烤炉里还热着干酪
And don't tell my hips, but I'm warming up a brie in the oven.
不错啊...
Nice. So...
嗯 什么事?
Mmm. What's up?
是这样的 我一直在仔细研究
Okay, well, I've been reading up on all the side effects
雌激素的所有副作用
you can get from estrogen,
发现...
and...
我需要你说实话
I need you to be honest with me.
我的胸部看起来变大没?
Do my boobs look bigger to you?
这个 有点难说啊
Well, it's kind of hard to tell.
Raj 你只要说"是或不是"
Come on, Raj, it's a "yes or no" question.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
等下
Um, wait.
那你跳起来 看看会不会乳摇
Jump up and down... let's see if they jiggle.
哦 不...
Uh, no, I...
我还是说不清...
I still can't tell, uh...
知道吗? 学哥这样做
Oh, you know what? Okay, uh, give me some of this.
真的吗?
Seriously?
你到底想不想搞清楚?
Do you want my help or not?
好吧
Fine.
好了
Okay, yup.
瞧 看上去... 觉得...
See, see, that... that looks like...
你的乳量还有增长的空间
that looks like they could be bigger.
但我觉得 我乳摇... 我乳摇起来
But you know, I bet... I bet when I do it,
也很波涛汹涌
mine do the same thing.
确实
Yeah, they kind of do.
好 让我感受一下
Hmm. Uh, let me see something.
温柔一点!
Hey, easy!
我的乳头很敏感的
My nipples are sensitive.
哦
Oh.
不好意思...
Sorry, sorry, uh...
好了
Okay.
我觉得...
I mean...
可能...
Yeah, m... maybe.
我也摸摸你的
Okay, let me feel.
不 我罩杯肯定比你大
No, I am definitely up a cup size.
但是... 你的胸部很坚挺
You know, b... but they're very firm,
这点挺不错的嘛
so you've got that going for you.
真的?
You think?
恩 恩 很挺拔
Yeah, yeah, yeah, very perky.
谢了
Thank you.
我真的很需要温暖人心的话
I really needed to hear that today.
干酪做好了!
Ooh, brie's ready!
耶!
Yay!
早上好
Good morning.
好啊
Hello.
那么今早是我送你去上班
So am I driving you to work
还是说仍旧对我生气?
or are you still mad at me?
我想搭你车
I'd like a ride.
如果你确实是把我
Assuming you actually do
送去学校的话
take me to work.
那我还能把你带哪儿去?
Where do you think I would take you?
谁知道呢?
Who knows?
你说你昨天才会到家
Uh, you said you'd be home yesterday,
但其实三天前就回来了
but you came home three days ago.
你说你带我去上班
You say you're taking me
但据我所知
to work, but for all I know,
我可能会被抛弃在废弃的游乐场里
I'll end up in a deserted amusement park.
或是玉米田里
Or a cornfield maze.
或者丢到小巷里去看狗咬狗
Or a back alley dog fight.
不如你说呢
You tell me.
我是去上班
I'm going to work.
你想就一起来吧
You can come if you want.
好啊
Okay.
你衬衣上有点东西
By the way, you have something on your shirt.
没有啊
No, I don't.
被欺骗的感觉不好受吧?
Hurts, doesn't it?
你知道 我怀疑
You know, I find myself wondering
你对我从来没说过真话
if anything you've ever told me is true.
我没能回来
I didn't make it back.
船把我沉向地狱了
The ship sank, I'm in hell.
你说你来自新泽西州 但我怎么相信你呢?
You say you're from New Jersey, but how can I believe you?
为什么会有人撒谎说
Why would anyone claim to be from New Jersey
来自新泽西呢?
if they weren't?
那倒是 我同意
All right, I'll give you that one.
我说过对不起了
Hey, I said I was sorry.
你还想怎么样呢?
What else do you want from me?
我要你承认 你的所作所为是错误的
I want you to admit that what you did was wrong.
好
Fine.
我做错了
What I did was wrong.
我倒是想相信你
I wish I could believe you.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我不会载你去上班了
I'm not driving you to work,
因为你实在是太讨厌了
because you're incredibly annoying.
真是典型的说一套 做一套
You say one thing and do the other,
那也就是说你肯定会载我 然后觉得我特讨人喜欢
so then you are driving me and you find me a delight.
- 别说了  - 继续说?
- Stop it.  - Keep it up?
再见!
Bye!
你好!
Hello!
你意思是你没有对我竖起中指?
So I guess you're really holding up the other four fingers?
嘿 怎么来得这么早啊?
Oh, hey, what are you doing here so early?
载Sheldon去学校
Driving Sheldon to work.
他还在生Leonard的气吗?
He's still mad at Leonard, huh?
他也在生你的气
Well, he's mad at you, too.
他说你是个邪恶的媚魔 专门诱惑他的好朋友
He says you're the succubus who led his friend astray.
我虽然不知道什么是媚魔 但是...
I don't know what "succubus" is, but...
有个"傻比"在里面 所以肯定不是个好东西
it has "suck" in it, so that can't be good.
就说听见你声音了
Thought I heard you out here.
嘿 Sheldon
Hey, Sheldon.
你可没有"嘿"
You don't get a "hey."
你有"哼"
You get a "hmm."
别这样
Come on, don't be like that.
我们前几个月在一起玩的多开心啊
We had so much fun together the last couple of months.
没错
You're right.
越是好朋友背叛我 我就越伤心
Which makes your betrayal all the more devastating.
Sheldon啊...
Sheldon...
我让你用我的超市会员卡
I let you buy feminine hygiene products
去买卫生巾
with my supermarket club card.
你知道我邮箱里有都是些
You have any idea the kind of coupons
什么东西的优惠宦?
I'm going to get in the mail now?
Sheldon 你和Leonard之间的争吵
Sheldon, your fight's with Leonard.
Penny可是无辜的...
Penny's got nothing to do...
注意立场 Amy
Careful, Amy.
我敌人女朋友的朋友也是我的敌人
The friend of my enemy's girlfriend is my enemy.
真的?
Really?
嗯
Yes.
要么站我这边 要么对立一面
You're either with me or against me.
你想做公交去上班?
You want to take the bus to work?
也许还有第三种选择
Maybe there's a third option.
顺带一提 早餐我还吃了甜甜圈
FYI, I had a doughnut for breakfast, you jerk.
所以我们只需要等待那些船上
So now we're just waiting for the data
获取的数据分析结果
from the ship to be crunched,
但看上去结果很不错
but the numbers look pretty promising.
那挺好的
That's so great.
如果你们能证明盎鲁效应...
If you guys prove the existence of Unruh radiation...
喂 喂!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
我眼睛在这儿
My eyes are up here.
嘿 Howard 你好 Raj
Howard, Raj.
犹大
Judas.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你是个疯子
You're a crazy person.
一个记忆力很好的疯子
A crazy person with a long memory,
如果再发展的话 就能生产出机器军队了
and if all goes according to plan, a robot army.
别说了
Stop it.
或者变异人部队
Or a mutant army.
要看创始人怎么想了
It depends on how my Kickstarter goes.
别说了!
I said, stop it!
听我说
Now, listen to me.
你们不只是朋友
You two aren't just friends.
你们是挚交
You're best friends.
这是多么美好阿
And that's a beautiful thing.
Leonard 你知道他为什么生气吗?
I mean, Leonard, you know why he's so mad at you?
因为他很想念你!
It's 'cause he missed you!
还有 作为朋友
Yeah, and as his friend,
你应该感到高兴
you should be happy
因为他还有着爱心
he has love in his life.
像我一样
As I do.
他昨天深深的抚摸着我的胸部
This man held my breast the other day,
我很爱他
and I love him for it.
声音太大了 哥们
A little loud, dude.
那么 我们能否放下过去的那些不愉快
So, can we please put aside these petty differences
然后高兴我们又重新在一起了呢?
and just be glad we're here together?
我想可以吧
Okay. I suppose so.
谢谢
Thank you.
不是什么变态的事情
Uh, it wasn't anything weird.
只是想知道他胸部到底多大
It was just to see how big they were.
然后Leonard带我去理发和看牙医
And then Leonard took me to the barber and the dentist,
然后愉快美好的一天
and then to cap off the perfect day,
就在参观洛杉矶度量局后结束
the Los Angeles Bureau of Weights and Measures.
我一开始觉得是主要讲"度"的
I thought the measures were going to be the stars
结果其实是讲"量"的
of the show; turns out it was the weights.
我真高兴你们重归于好
I'm so glad you guys are friends again.
也高兴能和你重归于好
And I'm glad you and I are friends again, too.
这倒提醒我
Aw. Which reminds me.
这是我邮箱里的 送给你
This came in the mail, and I want you to have it
"5毛钱卫生巾打折卡"
"50 cents off Vagisil."
用的时候记得我
Think of me when you apply it.
我说一句 其实我挺怀念我们一起玩耍的时候
Uh, can I just say, I've missed all of us hanging out together.
- 是  - 我也是
- Yeah.  - Me, too.
他啥时候能不用酒壮胆就在女生面前说话的?
Um, since when can Koothrappali talk in front of the girls without a beer?
在你离开不久的时候
Oh, that happened right after you left.
没人和我说过?
And no one told me?
我们居然忘记和他说了
Can't believe we forgot to tell him.
用的时候想着Sheldon
Think of Sheldon when you apply it.
(译者对tweepadock的解释: tweep是Twitter和Peeps的合成 指玩twitter的人 喜欢所有事都晒出来 Dock代指阴茎 有个笑话是大象的鼻子是阴茎 所以Amy用tweepadock代指了大象而且把私处都放鼻子上了 也指事情坦白了说 所以Sheldon说大象猜对了)